Bhai, everything is there here like normal home gyms,
there is nothing like that,
wow
sir, look, he can lift 5 kg dumbbells
and what about
Abesha in the train [laughs] go
down, hey, hey
grandfather, what are you doing, there is a competition going on,
guys, look between Amma and Babu, hey no, don't make it
bigger, hey don't do it, hey
guys, good morning, welcome to my new
vlog, so brother, finally today our gym work will be
completed.  So
I will show it to you today only after it is completed.  Because brother it has been two
days.  It will take the whole day today.
Then I will give you a complete tour of what
machines are there, what all we have installed, everything.
So brother, I am very excited and we will
also workout there tonight.  So let's see.
Hopefully it will happen because for the last two
days I was thinking that it will happen tomorrow itself but it did
not happen.  Let's go
inside for now.  Look how cool it looks.
grape arbor.  Now it will fit in completely and
then it will look even better.  So let's go inside.   Let me
show you what's going on, brother.   These days
mom is just busy with painting.
Look, I made this yesterday.
Hey, I made this today for half a month.
A month or two after Diwali.   Is
Diwali coming?   What else
?   Are
?   Give me just
two months.  So, preparations for Diwali started
2 months in advance.  Wow
guys
Kunal has come back from school.
Yes.
How is your day today?
Excellent.   Have fun
?   What else
?
So for now let's have lunch.  Today Bhaj
dal and rice are prepared.   Please
explain this a little, son.  What happened,
son?  There are so many utensils.  One or two is fine.
Tell me.  You are saying, my friend,
this is not happening to you.  They keep fighting every day.
Every day carrying utensils.  There is a fight every day
in the house.
Why do you keep fighting every day, friend?   Don't let
me sleep like this.
Hey friend, what will happen by doing this snotty thing
?   Guys,
I just made Avantiya
her favorite smoothie ball.   Thank
you.
Who says that we only fight?
Look,
I surprise you after a fight to
celebrate.  So guys, finally our gym is
complete.  Our family's
personal gym.  So now we're going to go look down.
We will see the family's reaction
and I have not seen it properly yet.
So let's take the whole family
to our gym and see the reaction and I will
also give you a complete tour.
Excited?   Let us go.   Let us go.
Now I won't be able to do everything brother.
Now everyone has to see whose body
will be made first?  Whose will be made first?
Amma's will be made first, brother.
Is it Amma?  Yes, mine will be strong.   Shall we go then
?   Let us go.   Let us go.   Let us go.   Let us go.   Let us go.
Brother, everything is there here like normal home gyms.  There is nothing like that in
it.
Wow.
But here there are machines for everything, brother.
Proper gym?   Are
?  Brother, everything has arrived.
Everyone came to the gym.
Sir, look at this, 5 kg dumbbell.   Will you pick it up
?  And what else,
take this oil,
all the oils are for Rs. 2.50 each, two and a half to five,
kiss me, there are a
lot of things here, I thought there would be only
one or two items,
look, elder mom, this is how it is done with these,
mom, the
whole gym is made, oh my, I
thought there would be only one or two items, two
friends, this is also there, look
Abesh in the train, he won't go even for
a minute, if he finds out,
he is
not bothering
[laughs]
oh oh oh oh brother, oh
nothing will happen, let him go, brother, the whole family has come to the gym and it is looking so good, look Saurda, I am enjoying it, friend, brother is doing it in full speed on the treadmill, Kunal is not able to hold it, oh
this is coming more,
aunty lifted the dumbbell, her
hands are heavy, very
guys, Amma is going to gym for the first time today.
Will you do it then?
Yes.
Come on, what should I get done?  Tell me what should I get done?
Brother, we will pick them up.
Will you lift dumbbells?
Come on Amma, let's make Amma lift the dumbbells.
2ai
Amma 2ai kilos.  Take 2.5 kg.
2 kg.  Amma,
take it Amma, 2 kg.   There
are suppressors.  Make your hands like this and
raise them like this.  Pick it up.
Hold it like this, like this, with your hand like this.  Look,
do it like this.  Do both of these like this.  Then
do it like this.   Do it, do it.
Move your hands like this.  Don't do it above.   You have to do this once.
Well, is
n't it feeling heavy?  Doesn't it feel heavy
?
No, it's okay.   Ca
n't you feel it?   Okay,
fine.   Do
this.
What are you doing, grandfather?   Do
n't kill each other a little.   To
grandfather.   Let's
turn it like this.  Turn it this way.  Yes, do it now.
Brother Amma Amma and Babu together.  There is a competition going on
guys.  Look between Amma and Babu.   Such is
grandfather.  Turn this way.  Do your hands like this.   Does
n't it feel heavy?   Is
n't it happening?   Does
n't it feel heavy?
No, okay.  I don't feel like it.
Papa ji, what are you doing?
Brother, the family had a lot of fun at the gym.
Everyone is doing something or the other.  So in this
way everyone will pay attention to their fitness.  I will keep doing
some gym or the other.
If I have my own house then it would be
a bit difficult to go to the gym as it was very far away.
Brother, look, let's keep Kunal's
time down brother.
You fell asleep upstairs.
Kunal, what are you doing?
These chests.
Oh wow.   That
's right, friend.
Look at it.  Well brother, the whole family
liked the gym.  Now I will
show you in detail which machines are there and what all
is there.  Complete tour of our gym.
So we made Brother Jim in our basement.
As you know, our
cool cars are also parked here.  Like
PS, GW, there is a jeep parked there also.  So
in this basement, in this area, we have built
our complete home gym.  So guys, here is
our treadmill which is a very
nice treadmill.  There
are a lot of options in this.  Look at this.
Starting off,
brother, this is awesome.  In this you
can do chest as well as abs.
And you can do it like this on the chest and you
can also do it while reclined.
Both wait, let's show it and
show it.  Look, look, you
can do such abs.  These are such apps,
such apps, it is okay
and try hitting your chest at the back
and keep your chest, bench press, oh my god, it
is great for bench press brother, try doing it like this,
friend,
this gym trainer will be beneficial, easily,
so on its right side here we have
these for doing squats etc., for doing shoulders, I
mean we can do a lot of things,
look at this and here is the cable
machine in which guys, if we want to do chest here, then we can do chest
from here
and then change its grip, like this
triceps, bicep, shoulder everything will be done.
Together
and can also hang up in it.   Yes.
Pull ups?   You
can also do pull ups.
Oh hang me too.
Kunali needs something to hang on to.
Walk and do pull ups.
Hit pull-ups.
Another bridge.
Kunali now I have to do it daily.  Daily exercise.
And guys, right next to this is the
deadlift area.  Look, we have created a complete platform
for deadlift.  So
look here there is a rod and 25-25.  This means 70 kg.
I love deadlifts.  So
I'm doing it right now with 70 kilos.  Oh, that's
great.  Let us go.
And look here there are all the plates for deadlift.
And next to it here is
this for the bag.
Lat pull down.
These are chests of bags.
Look at it this way.   You
can do it this way.
And they will also be installed somewhere else.
Ok?  Now you have to do it from below, you can do it from below also.   The
legs will be down, not the feet.  The feet
will remain down.  Look at this, look at this, look at this, something like this.
Next it's for the legs.
Leg Extension:
It has both leg extension and leg curl.   In
this way,
both are there for the legs.
Yes.  And look guys, there are so many dumbbells on its left.
So here's the whole rack.  In this, we have kept all the dumbbells from 2.5 to
5, 7.5, 10, 12.5, 17.5, 20, 25.
Both
sets are of 10 each.  12-12 K 7.5 K.  So look
how great this looks.
And to its left, we have placed two roads here.
And there is a bench placed here.
And there is one bench here.  And
look at all the weights here.  So, we have a complete gym.
All the exercises will be done.
So it is good for the whole family.   Easy Going.
Now Joshi family will also remain our healthy family.
Overall, one hour is required for this.
Yes.  Now I have to come to the basement anytime I get an hour a day.  You can
workout at
any time.  Because this is a bit of what happens when you go to the gym, you do
n't have to look at the timing.  There is
time for coming and going, there is crowd also.  But the
family will not face any problem here.   Easy Going.
Come to the basement whenever you feel like it.
Work out and go have fun.
And here the museum songs will play.
Right now the lights have to be installed here, the sound system has to be installed
and the main mirror has to be installed brother.  Guys, there will be
full mirrors on this wall.  There is a full
mirror so that you can see
what kind of body you are building while working out.  And our gym
is wide open.  Look,
we did not keep it completely full.  We have kept the middle area completely empty.  If
someone wants to do stretching, he can do it
or else I can do push ups.
So I can kill Easley.  Look, this is the
best thing.
So we have placed machines all around.  The
area in the middle is kept empty.  Here, if anyone wants to do
yoga or stretching, they can
do anything in the middle area.  This
is completely empty.  What happened Amma?   I am feeling
happy.  What is and
happy?
Yes.   At
this age?   The
mother from the gym.   One should
remain happy.  I am seeing this thing today.
Guys Amma has never gone to the gym in her life.  I have
come to the gym for the first time today.  That too
in his own home gym.
Babu, have you ever come?  Otherwise I am
saying that there is a gym in the village anyway.
Yes, there is a gym in the village.  Brother,
everyone picked up the dumbbells.
What challenge do you want to do?
Attack.
Attack?   What else
?
Attack.
Get it worshipped first.
Yes friend, it is necessary to perform puja first.
So for now let's start today's workout.
Today will be the first workout in our own
personal gym.
From tomorrow.   Are
?
Do it from tomorrow.
Why?
From tomorrow.
The puja will be done again in the morning.
Okay, shouldn't we do it now then?   That's what
I am saying.   Do the
puja.  What is morning?
Mummy, which God?   Let us
call Pandit ji.
Guys but elder mom is saying not to do it now.
First get the puja done and then do it from tomorrow morning.   That is
right, isn't it?
So come on brother, let's go out to the fields and
see what vegetables are grown there.
Then we will break it nicely.  So brother, look, the ladyfinger is getting
delicious and let's pluck it.   Are
you breaking it too?   Yes then.
Good.
I am also helping someone.
Here, put it in this.
In.  Babu has also come brother to pluck ladyfinger.
How colourful
are these roads, my heart beats on these roads.
Oh wow, grandfather is also singing the song 'Bhindi
Todto Todte'.  Your heart is
beating on the streets.  It is not beating on Amma.   Are
?
I know where Amma is.
Where is Amma?
Amma is doing gym.  Babu is plucking vegetables
here.
Yes, look how big this ladyfinger is.
Then you guys put it in it.
What
brother, now look, they are saying that we will do the wrong thing,
both of us will do it together, brother, you will
fall, you will fall together, don't do this brother,
press it, it will be fun, move away in your hand,
full speed, full speed, no no,
full speed, do
n't move, I will fall, if it hits my head, the person
behind me, it will be
fun,
I will catch you, if you fall,
now don't come from behind, all
three of you start running somewhere, hey
no friend, you will
spoil the machine, friend, today is your first day,
speed up and charge, hey it is your
first day, you will spoil the machine,
nothing, yes.  Oh no.  Big vote, big vote, don't do
this.  Big vote.  Reduced it, reduced it.
Sardar, I have become serious.  My
workout starts today.   There is
no sound.   There is
no sound.  There is no sound.
Mom is refusing brother.  Kunali?
So now everyone has gone, only Piyush and I are
here because brother it is feeling very nice, friend if you have your
own gym then look at that, Piyush has
even ordered a band brother, look what Piyush is
taking to the gym,
workout is not fun without songs,
now 30-30 songs will play,
put them on Karan Ojla, sometimes at mom's house, sometimes at
your home [music]
hey friend
Gaja
[music] guys,
now songs are playing in the gym downstairs and the
sound is coming upstairs too, see it is not too loud
and Chai ji's puja is going on.   Let's
take water to the gym.
[MUSIC]
Sir, look, I took a bath.   Did you
sweat in the gym?
And went.
So from now on, will you go to the gym daily?   What else
?  Gym tomorrow too.
Now there will be body pain tomorrow.   It will be a
lot of fun.  Sorry, look, today I have
made my own roti.   Will
you eat such a small roti after gym?   What else
?   Are
?   This
is my only tree.
So everyone is having dinner right now.  So right now I have come to my
room.  Now let me tell you
why we have built a gym at home.
What was the reason brother that we built a complete gym in the house?  The
reason was that I used to go in the morning at
5:00 am.  And at 5:00 in the morning
people used to stand outside the society.  Brothers used to follow me, man.  They did
n't even let me go to the gym.   Do you
understand?  That brother, I wake up in the morning and
go to the gym in my sleep so that I don't
find the crowd there late.  But even at 5:00 in the morning,
people knew I was leaving.  Then
people are following.  And
once the scene became quite intense.  So then
I thought that I will have to make it at home.  I can do it
well at home and I wo
n't have to go anywhere.  So that's the only
reason guys.  Something had happened.  Rest, see you
in the next vlog.  Thank you so much
for watching.  Bye.
[Music]
OK